Number one
K-content channel.
tvN for joy.
Fifteen.
THE FOLLOWING PROGRAM IS
NOT SUITABLE FOR VIEWERS UNDER 15.
VIEWER DISCRETION IS ADVISED.
THIS PROGRAM CONTAINS PRODUCT PLACEMENTS
AND VIRTUAL ADVERTISING.
MY BIAS, MY BOSS
PRODUCTION SUPPORTED BY:
MINISTRY OF CULTURE, SPORTS AND TOURISM
KOREA CREATIVE CONTENT AGENCY
THIS DRAMA
IS A WORK OF FICTION
CHILD AND ANIMAL SCENES WERE FILMED SAFELY
UNDER EXPERT SUPERVISION
How can Mr. Kang be fine?
That was just an accident.
I mean, a minor fender bender.
A minor collision.
Right, a fender bender.
I was just reaching out for this.
The wind blew out of nowhere.
Exactly.
It flew off. I don't know why this...
Then again, he's clearly
not inexperienced like me.
Well, then.
Get home safe.
Oh, okay. You too.
Thank you for today.
Good night.
Am I the only one shaken up?
That was just an accident.
I mean, a minor fender bender.
A minor collision.
That was
my very first kiss.
He's so unfazed.
He's such a pro.
Why is my heart racing like this?
CHAN
Da-reum, did you make it home okay?
What's wrong with me?
Another guy friend...
Da-reum, did you have
trouble sleeping last night?
- You look pretty tired.
- I know.
I was
wide awake all night.
What kept you so wide awake?
We all have those days.
Hello, sir.
- Good morning.
- Let me through.
- Excuse me.
- The doors are closing.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- What is it?
- Sorry.
- Jeez.
- What...
Well, let me...
- Excuse me.
- I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
Mr. Kang?
I'm standing behind you.
I'm right here.
It's Lee Min-a. I'm right here.
I guess
it's awkward only for me.
Can't he see me?
THE PALACE WHERE THE WIND RESTS
Chan.
Thank you for the quick decision.
Not at all. I couldn't sleep a wink
after getting the offer yesterday.
It's always been my dream
to work with you.
Well, then.
I'll reach out after our final talk
with the US co-producers.
I doubt there will be any issues.
I see. If you give me the chance,
I won't let you down.
This project will be filmed
entirely on location in LA.
Take a look at this.
Once you're confirmed for the role
why don't you head over early
to get a feel for the local vibe?
The US team even booked a villa.
You could relax
like you're on vacation
and do occasional meetings
or readings.
It sounds like a good idea.
It could help with the jet lag too.
I'd love that.
From the looks of it,
it's practically confirmed.
Congratulations.
You've always talked about Hollywood,
and now, your dream is coming true.
It's all thanks to you.
I'd better sort out
your local schedule first.
Do you think we'll be
in the States for a while?
Probably. It's an all-location shoot.
But it'll definitely make
your career skyrocket.
DA-REUM, DID YOU MAKE IT HOME OKAY?
DA-REUM:
YES, I'M HOME SAFE. GET SOME REST!
Are you dating someone?
Chan.
You've had paparazzi on you for days.
And this is a crucial time.
I know.
Hello, Mr. Kang.
Hello, Ms. Da-reum.
- Are you buying something for Kung?
- Right.
Does Jjak like this too?
Oh, totally.
The second I grab this,
its eyes change like a hunter.
I guess
I'll have to buy one for each.
How come
you aren't working late today?
I work overtime from home these days.
I felt like
Kung was waiting for me all day.
Same here.
Do you want to meet outside?
Sure.
Wait, what?
No, I mean...
For Kung and Jjak.
So they can play together.
I see.
That caught me off guard.
Oh, well.
I guess I wasn't the only one.
INCOMING CALL: CHAN
- Just a moment.
- Oh, okay.
Hey.
I was actually going to call you
when I got home.
No, I'm okay.
Yes, I got home safely yesterday.
Oh, how did that important thing go?
It went well. Thanks.
That's a relief.
Da-reum, there's something
I really need to tell you.
Are you free tomorrow evening?
I'll text you the address.
Let's meet after work.
Okay.
Oh, and...
I'm sorry. I'll call you back later.
- Okay, bye.
- Bye.
- Sorry about that.
- It's fine.
Don't tell me
it's that guy from the blind date.
What?
Yes, it's him.
How can he call
after ditching you like that?
I guess he felt bad.
If he was going to feel bad,
he shouldn't have left you there.
He's not a celebrity or anything.
What could possibly
make him that busy?
Beats me.
Do you realize
you just said, "I'm okay" again?
Did I do that again?
Whoever he is
you don't need to put up
with him that much.
You're right.
To be honest
it wasn't a blind date.
I've liked him for a very long time.
But now that
I'm actually seeing him...
I find myself
accommodating him
even without him asking.
I always prioritize his situation
over mine
and my own feelings get pushed aside.
I'm honestly
feeling a bit lost.
Then set one rule for yourself.
Ask yourself...
if this relationship
makes you more like yourself
or if it makes you
feel smaller.
Whatever choice you make
just make sure it's a choice
that's true to who you are.
- The payment is complete.
- All set.
It wasn't a blind date.
I've liked him for a very long time.
She liked him...
for a long time.
It wasn't me.
I wasn't the one.
I'll give it a try.
I'm going to be myself from now on.
I like you.
This is so annoying.
That guy...
Who the heck is he?
HELLO, HA-GI
ASK ME ANYTHING YOU WANT
MEETING YOUR LONG-TIME CRUSH
AND REALIZING THEY AREN'T
ALL THAT
- Would you like
- Oh, my goodness.
some helpful information
about your recent search?
All right.
Let's hear it.
It's totally normal to feel let down
when you finally meet someone
you've spent a long time idealizing.
It stems from the gap
between expectation and reality.
Right?
It's better to date someone
who actually likes you
than chasing an unrequited love.
Don't you think?
Statistically speaking,
stable relationships are often built
not with a long-term crush
but with someone close by
who expresses their feelings first.
Someone close by?
Yes, close by.
DIY KNOT KEYCHAIN KIT
BY KNOT MASTER IM CHEONG-RIM
UNFRAMED: KNOTTING
UNTYING TRADITIONS TO TIE IT ANEW
Great work.
Let's proceed with this plan.
Yes, sir. I'll do my best.
Ms. Nam.
Yes?
Do you have plans tonight?
Excuse me?
Well...
We should get Kung and Jjak
together sometime.
But I already have
a prior engagement tonight.
Then let me know when you're free.
Yes, sir.
A prior engagement?
She already has plans?
Could it be with that guy?
I'm sorry. I'll call you back later.
No way.
It can't be.
Welcome. Right this way, please.
Okay, thank you.
Sir.
- Hi.
- Hello.
Let me know
if you need anything at all.
Thank you.
Why did you want to see me here?
I have something to celebrate.
I figured we could do some shopping
and have a date.
Why don't you try this on?
- This?
- I think it'll look great on you.
It's gorgeous.
What do you think?
I like it.
You pull off neutral tones
really well.
It looks amazing on you.
Try this one too.
Oh, I highly doubt
this one will suit me.
You never know until you try it on.
Looks weird, doesn't it?
Not at all.
You look beautiful in it.
I hardly wear clothes like this.
That's exactly why I like it.
It's nice to see
this style suits you.
Da-reum, come here.
This would be a great outfit for LA.
LA?
Yes.
So it's practically confirmed.
Working with Director Park Chan-dong!
That's incredible.
They're still confirming the details.
But I wanted you
to be the first to know.
It's all thanks to your support.
- Thank you, Da-reum.
- Not at all.
I'm so happy for you.
Does that mean
the shoot will take place
in the States?
Yes.
We begin production in LA
early next year.
The exact dates
aren't set yet, though.
I guess...
I won't see you for a while.
Why don't you come with me?
Pardon?
They're providing
a car and a place for me there.
You could study fashion
while I'm filming.
Then we wouldn't have to be apart.
What about the company?
We can work that out.
A lot of people
work remotely these days.
Building experience there
could be better for you.
You'd love it.
LA is full
of fashion shows and brands.
That does sound nice.
In that sense
I picked one for you too.
I actually have
something for you too.
What is it?
A cardholder?
Yes, I made it myself
at a leather workshop.
This is really well-made.
It's too precious to use.
Thanks.
LA...
Whatever choice you make
just make sure it's a choice
that's true to who you are.
FASHION DIRECTOR NAM DA-REUM!
APPELLO'S EMPLOYEE OF THE YEAR!
UNFRAMED: KNOTTING
UNTYING TRADITIONS TO TIE IT ANEW
APPELLO BRAND EXPANSION PROPOSAL
Exhale on your way up.
Inhale on your way down.
Come up just a little higher.
Hold it right here. One, two.
All right.
We're done for today.
Please tidy up your space.
Okay.
- Great work.
- Thank you so much.
Well...
Mr. Min-woo, will you come
to the last lesson
of the day next time?
I'm pretty sure she gave me a sign.
Was I wrong?
Thank you for the last session today.
- You too.
- Right.
I'll get going, then. Goodbye.
Really, I'm leaving.
- Mr. Min-woo.
- Yes?
We should head out together.
Right? We're grabbing a bite, right?
- Shall we?
- Let's go.
Wow, that looks so good.
- You must be starving.
- Thank you.
Today's session was tough, wasn't it?
Not at all. It was a breeze.
Thank you.
You must be pretty extroverted
to hit on someone
at a place like this.
How did you get here?
- I took a bus.
- Then on your way back
you can take a chance on me.
Oh, you remember that?
That was a first for me.
Seriously.
I'm actually a total introvert.
I've never dated anyone.
That day
I fell for you and gathered
the courage for the first time ever.
Is that your go-to pickup line?
Yes.
Just kidding.
I tend to ramble a bit
when I'm around someone I like.
- Why?
- To act like I'm not nervous.
What about now, then?
I'm completely like this.
Did that make you laugh?
Guess that's a win.
Anyway
thank you so much for handling
that awful customer the other day.
Don't mention it.
How do you know
all the terms and conditions, though?
No one actually reads those.
It's a habit.
The habit of wanting to win
the moment an argument breaks out.
- It's your habit?
- It's just that
reading text is part of my job.
Who is he, really?
There's a surprising side to him.
BUCKET LIST FOR LA
It's been updated.
You've added an LA version too.
You've always said making it
to Hollywood was your dream.
Right.
So naturally,
I spent a lot of time picturing it.
We can cross these off together.
We'll enjoy the night view
at the observatory
and walk along the beach together.
It's a perfect date itinerary.
Chan.
I have something to say.
Something to say?
You see
I really enjoyed
our time together,
and I definitely had butterflies.
But then...
I don't think
I was being honest.
What do you mean?
With you
and
with myself.
So today
I'm going to stop pretending I'm okay
and just be honest.
I thought if I were with someone I like
I'd be able to share
my feelings with him
by laughing, crying
whining, and even fighting.
But for some reason...
I couldn't easily do that
with you.
I think
I still see you
more as an idol
rather than
a romantic partner.
I still root for your dreams.
But I have my own dreams
to chase now.
The US sounds great
but I love Appello.
I love
the work I do here.
So I'd rather just
stay as Nam Da-reum,
an employee of Appello...
and remain...
your fan.
CHRYSANTHEMUM KNOT
DONGSIMGYEOL KNOT
Here we go.
Nam Da-reum mode activated.
Nam Da-reum mode?
What does that mean?
Remember when we made
the challenge video?
She worked even harder
when she was told to back off.
She thrives when pushed to the brink.
I call it Nam Da-reum mode.
Ms. Da-reum, you aren't being pushed
to the edge again, are you?
Not at all. I just like doing it
because it keeps
my mind from wandering.
What happened to your hand?
Did you injure yourself?
I'm currently fostering a kitten.
I need to find someone to adopt it
but I've been too busy to even try.
A cat? I've actually been
preparing to adopt one.
Hold on. Can I see a picture?
- Really?
- Yes.
Just a second.
- Do you like animals?
- Yes, totally.
Me too.
Isn't it adorable?
The name is Jjak.
There are actually two.
Their names are Kung and Jjak,
like a matching beat.
Oh, my gosh. It's adorable.
No joke, I've wanted an orange tabby.
- Are you serious?
- Dead serious.
Here's another one.
- Adorable, right?
- Oh, my. It's so cute.
This is the script
from Director Park Chan-dong.
Chan, your casting is finalized!
THE TARGET: THE LAST AIM
- What is it? You can't believe it?
- What?
No, it's just that
things are going so well.
Is that really your concern?
Wait, all right.
Let's celebrate later.
Since it's all shot in the States,
we've got tons to do.
Clearing schedules, sorting visas,
getting you in shape...
And if you need anything,
just write it down.
Won-bin,
I can't let it end like this.
Chan, where are you going?
Mr. Kang.
You're still here?
I'm going to finish a bit more.
You really don't have to...
Thank you.
No date tonight?
No.
I'm way
too swamped for that right now.
Why are you doing
all this by yourself?
I never gave such an order.
My coworkers helped out a lot
during the day.
I'm just finishing up what's left.
It must be hard
taking on a major event
all of a sudden.
It's a little overwhelming.
Still, it feels rewarding
to be in charge of something.
You'll learn a lot
from each project you handle.
Right.
Oh, right.
Young-woo said
he wanted to adopt Kung and Jjak.
You're sending them away already?
I'm upset about it a bit too
but it's great for Kung and Jjak.
It is.
I bought Kung lots of toys.
What else did you get?
I said you didn't have to.
Still.
Where did you get them?
From stores and stuff.
Ms. Da-reum?
She's working late today.
Mr. Kang.
Do you remember
what you said to me last time?
What did I say?
That whatever choice I make
I should make sure
I'd be true to who I am.
Thanks to what you said
I could pluck up the courage.
For the first time ever
I was able to be honest.
And I made a choice
that was true to myself.
Thank you, Mr. Kang.
You were just someone
who was always capable
of making that choice.
It seems more like it
now that you put it into words.
She broke it off with that guy, then.
- Ms. Da-reum.
- Yes?
I have something to...
I see you're hard at work.
Why are you here?
I heard you stayed behind
to prepare for the pop-up.
Is this the DIY kit?
Yes, Director.
How is it made? Teach me.
Take a seat.
You work so fast, Director.
I once signed
over 1,000 albums in a day.
This is nothing.
Fold it properly.
Focus on the detail,
not just the speed.
Yes, boss.
Ms. Da-reum. Check this.
So, Ms. Da-reum.
Who are you a better match with
between us two?
Sorry?
Why do you want to know that?
Everyone has a type.
I'm still new, so I can't say.
And you two are so different.
What a safe, political reply.
I just wanted to know
if you were leaning toward anyone.
We need to talk.
Did you really
come here today about work?
Why?
And when you came
to Master Im's place?
Because this is an important project.
Do you
like Ms. Da-reum?
I do like her.
She's my favorite employee.
Who wouldn't like someone
who works so hard?
Only as an employee?
What do you want me to say?
You tried to go after her just now.
What about you, then?
Are you protecting your employee
or are you keeping me in check?
You won't answer either.
Once you decide to become honest
so will I.
Ms. Da-reum.
Who are you a better match with
between us two?
I want to start dating you.
Da-reum.
I'm sorry for that day.
Please don't mind me.
I feel bad
to send you home like this.
I'm really fine.
But you're not okay.
At least, in front of me
you can say it's not okay.
I just wanted to know
if you were leaning toward anyone.
Coming!
Hi, thank you.
Enjoy the food and have a happy day.
Have a happy day.
I hope my voice brings you
a small piece of happiness
every single day.
This is Roy from D.N.X signing off.
That was most definitely Roy's voice.
I wanted to have kalguksu today.
We failed yet again today.
When will we ever get to eat there?
We don't stand a chance
unless we take the morning off
to wait in line.
I really wanted to try out
Kalguksu Jip.
Me too.
Shall we go to the rooftop
for a stroll to digest our lunch?
- Good idea.
- Isn't it?
I have some work to get back to.
Ms. Min-a, shall we go, then?
Yes, sure.
- See you later.
- Bye.
See you in a bit.
You didn't go out to lunch, Ms. Seo?
I'm leaving now.
I see you had an early lunch.
- Yes. Enjoy your meal.
- Thanks.
Did the cleaning lady come by?
It looks like you're running away.
Why's there so much stuff for a cat?
I kept buying stuff.
Here, hand over the cat
and tell her how you feel.
What are you on about?
Don't miss out
on an opportunity like this.
- Good luck over there.
- What the heck?
Go on home.
Good luck, okay? Do your thing.
I'm leaving.
How I feel?
Tell her how you feel.
Someone close by.
Hang on.
I'll come by around 8 p.m.
Great. Kung and Jjak
will meet at last.
There's a lot of stuff,
so I'll come to your place.
I'm setting off now.
He's so considerate.
See you again, Da-reum.
If Mr. Kang sees this...
No!
Am I done?
Tell her how you feel.
Hello, Kung.
Wait here.
That must've been heavy.
Thank you, Mr. Kang.
Wear these.
- The thing is...
- Yes?
It's my first time
visiting a lady's home.
I hope you don't mind the intrusion.
It's fine. Make yourself at home.
You can take your time.
Have some tea.
Thanks.
Jjak.
Listen. Kung is here to see you.
They've grown a lot.
You think so?
Isn't Kung the same size?
Kung is...
Where's Kung?
Kung.
When did it get in there?
I'll go get Kung.
- Kung.
- What?
You wait here. Oh, no.
Kung?
- Wait!
- Scared me.
You can't go in there. Not ever.
It's my secret...
It's my underwear closet.
I apologize.
Then...
I won't even take a peek.
Sit over there and wait.
- I'll get Kung and join you.
- Okay.
- I don't see a thing right now.
- Good.
SHINING BRIGHT, LEE CHAN
That was
the biggest crisis of my life.
I can't hide that I'm Chan's fan
from Mr. Kang forever.
Should I just
tell him the truth?
They really recognize each other.
Isn't that fascinating?
You said they fought
and ate each other's food
when they were together.
They fight when they're together
and miss each other when apart.
It must be like that
for people...
and for cats, too.
Yes. Now is the time.
Mr. Kang.
The truth is...
Yes?
So...
- For a long time...
- Excuse me.
Yes, hello.
I'm not at home.
I'll check when I get back.
- What were you about to say?
- What?
Oh, I was going to thank you
for bringing Kung.
I should thank you.
I did bring Kung over
but I got to see Jjak again.
And I got to see you again.
It's nice.
Look at the time.
- I should go.
- That's so sudden.
You should rest.
Kung, I'm leaving.
I'll see you at work, then.
- Drive home safely, Mr. Kang.
- Bye.
Did she get the message?
I got to see you again.
It's nice.
"I got to see you again.
It's nice."
I agree.
Yes, that's right.
How did you get the company photos?
Oh, really? No wonder.
I look forward to your article.
- Hello.
- Hi. Sit over here, please.
- I'll get everything ready.
- Okay.
I heard you'll be working
with Director Park Chan-dong.
- I'm really happy for you.
- Thanks.
I'm working
on a global project of my own.
We're filming in the US.
- In the US?
- Yes.
What interesting timing.
It looks like
we're meant to keep crossing paths.
They're so adorable.
I couldn't sleep for days.
They're so cute.
Oh, my gosh.
- Hi.
- Hello.
You're leaving together?
Yes. He's coming by to get the cats.
I'm on my way home, too.
I'll tag along.
I'll drive you there.
- We're headed in the same direction.
- I'd like that.
Kung and Jjak. Look after yourselves.
Don't forget me, okay?
- Bye.
- Take care.
I'll take really good care
of Kung and Jjak.
Mr. Kang. Thank you so much
for helping with the luggage.
Bye, Young-woo.
If you don't mind me asking,
do you think...
Never mind.
By any chance...
Wouldn't it be a shame
to part like this?
Since we're coworkers
how about some coffee
with Mr. Kang too?
That's a no.
Cats get very stressed out
in unfamiliar settings.
They need their owner
on their first day.
Yes, right, of course.
You're the CEO for a reason.
- Let's pass on it today.
- Yes. Maybe next time.
Go on home
and help the cats settle in.
I'll do that. Goodbye.
Bye.
Ms. Da-reum.
Let's hang out soon.
Without Mr. Kang.
Sounds good.
Kung, Jjak, live happily ever after.
Look after each other.
Don't fight.
Ms. Da-reum. Are you crying?
No.
I guess I got attached to them.
I think
I got more attached.
I liked asking each day
if they'd eaten.
The weird photos too.
I looked forward to them.
Yes.
Now the cats are gone.
I have no reason to contact you.
Well...
What's wrong with me?
Shall we have dinner together?
It would be a shame
to part like this.
Sure. I'd like that.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Next. Come on in.
I really wanted to try this place.
How did you hear about it?
Well...
KALGUKSU JIP
- I heard they're famous.
- They are.
We failed yet again today.
When will we ever get to eat there?
I really wanted to try out
Kalguksu Jip.
- Me, too.
- Kalguksu?
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING FOR?
Famous kalguksu places nearby.
I found it.
- You wanted to try this that much?
- Yes.
They don't take reservations,
so it's really hard to get in.
Over here.
Sorry about that.
Stand on this side.
Thank you.
Two bowls of kalguksu.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy yourselves.
Look at the color of the broth.
There's no way this isn't good.
Okay, just a moment, please.
- More pickled radish, please.
- Leave that here.
What is it?
Do you not like it?
This tastes amazing.
Right? They're famous for a reason.
Let's dig in.
It's good.
That was awesome.
- It was worth the wait, wasn't it?
- Yes.
Mr. Kang, look at that.
STAR GAME ARCADE
Doesn't that look like Jjak?
That expression
and the light-lipped mouth.
It's totally Jjak.
How cute.
- Do you want it?
- What?
Mr. Kang.
INSERT COIN HERE
Yes, I got it.
Darn it!
Mr. Kang, that's enough.
Watching you
was more than enough fun.
- No, I see the pattern now.
- What?
The claw's pressure is consistent
but if you look carefully,
it's skewed slightly to the left.
I failed just now
because the angle was wrong.
Mr. Kang. Why are you
so serious about this?
We have a goal.
We want Jjak.
It's time to end it.
You selected the angle
and chose a strategy.
You looked almost professional.
I wanted to get you
the Jjak lookalike.
- Sorry.
- Don't be.
This is more than cute.
You were cute, too.
I had...
fun today.
So did I.
Also...
Kung and Jjak left
but you can still contact me
for no reason.
I liked
listening to whatever...
you had to say.
Listen.
Not as your CEO...
but as Kang Ha-gi...
I want to...
Excuse me.
TEAM MANAGER KIM MI-YOUNG
REPORTER PARK MIN-HA
- Hi, Seul-a.
- Hey!
There's a scandal about you and Chan.
There are articles
with photos of you two together.
What?
THEY SEEMED
TO BE ENJOYING THEIR DATE
Mr. Kang.
Is this...
Is this true?
MY BIAS, MY BOSS
EPILOGUE
Ms. Da-reum.
Who are you a better match with
between us two?
I just wanted to know
if you were leaning toward anyone.
KUNG AND JJAK?
HA-GI AND DA-REUM?
You went on a date,
but you're not dating?
That's basically a stalker,
not a stalker fan.
- Boycott Appello!
Mr. Kang's not in.
Da-reum got branded
a stalker fan because of me.
It's not the kind of relationship
that people think.
Were you honest when I asked
how you felt about Da-reum?
Sort it out in person.
Are you doing this to me
to protect that one girl?
I won't blame you
even if you fire me.
Do you have to go this far?
As of this moment, Ms. Da-reum...
I don't want to be
a nuisance to the company.
Subtitles by Eunjin Erica Kim
and Jennifer Jean Lim
Synced and corrected by
WEISSACHsubs